[{"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Scream-3.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Who is this", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " And that that place chick wasn't that bad either but I'm really concerned about my safety now", "docId": "Scream-3.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " SCENE 32. INT. CANDY'S LIVING ROOM", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Well, that would explain my constant headaches", "docId": "Scream-3.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Thank you.  I'm sorry that things didn't work out with my friend, but being single, that's a pretty good fall back", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Someone", "docId": "Scream-3.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Lost and lonely what", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " U", "docId": "Scream-3.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " No I need to call you. Just you", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Scream-3.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Who's this", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "It's not just a new script, it's a new movie", "docId": "Scream-3.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "My movie", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "That's because I didn't", "docId": "Scream-3.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "What meeting", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Do you wanna have this conversation with a polygraph", "docId": "Scream-3.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "When it's a threat, you'll know it", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Is that a threat, Detective", "docId": "Scream-3.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " Is that a threat", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Geez", "docId": "Scream-3.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Being my friend.  What the hell are you doing", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What the hell are you doing", "docId": "Scream-3.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I am my friend", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What do you know about trilogies", "docId": "Scream-3.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You seem to like movies, Detective", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "You seem to like movies, Detective", "docId": "Scream-3.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I'll call you Mark when you catch the killer, Detective", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I used to think I had the perfect mom, perfect family.  Till I found out I was wrong.  She had a secret life, and I tried to understand that, and soon as I thought I had, more secrets.  I don't' know who my mom was.  Sometimes I feel like I'm just learning about my mother for the first time. You know, with TV and those movies and what not. God sometimes I feel like I'm just learning about myself for the first time. Like I'm watching my life instead of living in it", "docId": "Scream-3.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "How is that good news", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " Who is this", "docId": "Scream-3.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " Um w", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Um w", "docId": "Scream-3.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "my friend, my friend, whoever, um, call me back, I can only hear myself", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "{ a click", "docId": "Scream-3.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "The question isn't who I am.  The question is, who's with me", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Always hard being friends with you, my friend. When you're friends with my friend, you die! Well these friends don't have to, my friend. It's up to you", "docId": "Scream-3.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Are real?  How do you know you're not hearing things? How do you know I'm not someone in your head? Somewhere, you know", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Gale he's got my friend", "docId": "Scream-3.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I know", "qsentId": 40}]